<resources>
    <string name="app_name">San José Tour</string>

    <!-- The source for the descriptions was Wikipedia for all of the places that had articles there.
    Otherwise, some descriptions were took from each of the official websites,
    or from reviews website such as www.the10best.com -->

    <string name="category_culture">Culture</string>
    <string name="category_shopping">Shopping</string>
    <string name="category_dining">Dining</string>
    <string name="category_nightlife">Nightlife</string>
    <string name="directions">Directions</string>
    <string name="call">Call</string>
    <string name="website">Website</string>
    <string name="national_theater">National Theater</string>
    <string name="melico_salazar_theater">Melico Salazar Theater</string>
    <string name="pre_columbian_gold_museum">Pre-Columbian Gold Museum</string>
    <string name="center_science_culture">Center of Science and Culture</string>
    <string name="jade_museum">Jade Museum</string>
    <string name="art_museum">Art Museum</string>
    <string name="national_museum">National Museum</string>
    <string name="national_theater_description">Located in the central section of San José, Costa Rica. Its construction began in 1891, and it opened to the public on 21 October 1897 with a performance of Johann Wolfgang von Goethe\'s Faust.  The National Theatre stood as a cultural asset of the country during a time when coffee exports were a source of its success. It presents high quality performances, with artistic criteria being very high.  The building is considered the finest historic building in the capital, and it is known for its exquisite interior which includes its lavish furnishings.</string>
    <string name="melico_salazar_description">The Melico Salazar Theatre is located in San José, Costa Rica. It maintains a full schedule of concerts, recitals, and plays.  While large and built in the European Baroque style, it is far simpler than the Parisian influenced Teatro Nacional one block east.</string>
    <string name="pre_columbian_gold_museum_description">The Pre-Columbian Gold Museum is a museum in San José, Costa Rica. It is located in a subterranean building underneath the Plaza de la cultura and is managed by the Banco Central de Costa Rica.</string>
    <string name="center_science_culture_description">Centro Costarricense de la Ciencia y la Cultura is a science and culture museum complex in Costa Rica. Located in a fortress-like building that once served as the central penitentiary between 1910 and 1979, the center was inaugurated in 1994.</string>
    <string name="jade_museum_description">The Museo del Jade \"Marco Fidel Tristán Castro\" is an archaeological museum in San José, Costa Rica. It is since 2014 located in front of Plaza de la Democracia. It was founded in 1977 by Fidel Tristán Castro, the first president of the INS.</string>
    <string name="art_museum_description">The Costarrican Art Museum is the country\'s main institute dedicated to the conservation, exhibition and promotion of  plastic arts. Its collection is composed of around 6000 art pieces from national and international artists about several artistic disciplines, including mostly painting, sculpture and photography. It is located in the same building as the very first international airport in Costa Rica, which was known as \"Aeropuerto El Coco\", in La Sabana Metropolitan Park.</string>
    <string name="national_museum_description">The National Museum of Costa Rica is located at Calle 17, between Central and Second Avenue, Cuesta de Moras, in the Bellavista Fortress, a crenallated, ochre colored building opposite the Legislative Assembly of Costa Rica. The fortress was built in 1917 and was originally a military barracks: the exterior walls still have many bullets lodged in them from the country\'s 1948 civil war. It became the site of the museum in 1950.</string>
    <string name="multiplaza_curridabat">Multiplaza Curridabat</string>
    <string name="multiplaza_escazu">Multiplaza Escazú</string>
    <string name="mall_san_pedro">Mall San Pedro</string>
    <string name="multicentro_desamparados">Multicentro Desamparados</string>
    <string name="lincoln_plaza">Lincoln Plaza</string>
    <string name="multiplaza_escazu_description">Multiplaza Escazú is located in Escazú, Costa Rica. It has a movie theater, and a large food court. It is also home to many international brands like: Zara, Nike, Mango, Lacoste, Armani Exchange, Tommy Hilfiger, Calvin Klein, Carolina Herrera, Salvatore Ferragamo, Cartier, Steve Madden, Tiffany and Co., Guess, Furla, Massimo Dutti, Diesel, Hugo Boss, and many others. It has gone under five renovations making it the largest mall in Costa Rica, and the most luxurious.</string>
    <string name="multiplaza_curridabat_description">Multiplaza Curridabat opened to the public in October 2003 and was expanded and completely renovated in 2014, it is located in east San José. Multiplaza Curridabat offers visitors over 160 stores including Siman, Universal, Forever 21, Zara, Bershka, Stradivarius, Pull and Bear, Steve Madden, Tommy Hilfiger, Columbia, Mango, and Springfield, as well as a large food court, Cinemark movie theaters, a financial center and casual dine-in options including Chili’s, Rostipollos, Johnny Rockets and Pizza Hut. In total, Multiplaza Curridabat extends over 53,000 m2 and offers more than 1,500 covered parking spaces.</string>
    <string name="mall_san_pedro_description">Located just a short distance from San José proper in San Pedro, this large shopping mall offers four stories of shopping diversions. A wide variety of boutiques, specialty shops, gift shops, clothing stores and department stores sell everything you\'d hope to find in a mall, and then some. Additionally, a large movie theater, gaming arcades and two discos add to the fun of this lively establishment. A food court offers a number of different dining options, from International eats to fast food. This mall is popular with students from the nearby colleges, who flock to the arcades and food court after class.</string>
    <string name="multicentro_desamparados_description">Multicentro Desamparados is located in southern San José, and is home to 170 stores including banks, restaurants and clothing stores. It has over 700 parking spaces both outdoors and in underground parking. Some of the main attractions include Universal, Garper, Aliss and the Cinepolis movie theater.</string>
    <string name="lincoln_plaza_description">Open since 2012, Lincoln Plaza is located in Moravia, San José. It has over 170 commercial locations including stores, movie theaters, restaurants and a food court. Some of its main stores are Springfield, Mas x Menos, Smashburger, Forever21, Timberland, Arturo Calle and Starbucks.</string>
    <string name="le_monastere">Le Monastère</string>
    <string name="le_chandelier">Le Chandelier</string>
    <string name="machu_picchu">Machu Picchu</string>
    <string name="fogo_brasil">Fogo Brasil</string>
    <string name="la_divina_comida">La Divina Comida</string>
    <string name="le_monastere_description">Situated on a hillside overlooking the San José metropolitan area in Costa Rica, Le Monastère represents a combination of quiet reflection and full-blown festivity, expertly mixed to please all facets of the dining and nightlife spectrum. The restaurant boasts an eclectic history. Originally the home and chapel of an elite family in the early 1900’s, the buildings were later converted into a monastery for religious novitiates (of an unknown denomination). Today, the site hosts one of Central America’s best restaurants.</string>
    <string name="le_chandelier_description">Le Chandelier Restaurant has been serving gourmet French cuisine since it opened in 1985.  Located in Montes de Oca in Los Yoses, Le Chandelier is known as the meeting point for gourmet food connoisseurs both nationally and internationally. Owner and chef, Don Claude Dubuis, serves up unique, authentic French cuisine including meats, soups, fresh fish and more, followed by an extensive French wine list from the best wineries in the country.</string>
    <string name="machu_picchu_description">Machhu Picchu is the place to savor such succulent dishes like the lemon-flavored mashed potatoes stuffed with shrimp and the chicken craklings, bite-sized chicken pieces served with a savory tartar sauce. The seafood platter is generous enough to serve two and loaded with shrimp, squid and conch cooked multiple ways. The bar serves beer, wine, and pisco sour, a Peruvian cocktail crafted from grape liquor. Machu Picchu is the site to taste and sample some of the best Peruvian flavors in San José, Costa Rica.</string>
    <string name="fogo_brasil_description">Fogo Brasil Restaurant has captured the culinary art from Southern Brazil to bring a menu based on a traditional Gaucho Churrascaria. The menu is typical for a Brazilian steak house and you can experience the waiters around your table with skewers of meat that they shave onto you plate. Besides steak, they also offer chicken, lamb, pork, and some Brazilian specialties of fraldinha, feijoada, guarniciones, maminha, costela</string>
    <string name="la_divina_comida_description">La Divina Comida is a modern restaurant on Avenida Escazú that offers a unique dining experience, great service, delicious Peruvian food and an inviting atmosphere. Chef Marco Antonio Ganoza is passionate about the dishes he creates and his love of food can practically be tasted in each bite. The sleek modern decor complements plates that are rich in flavor and stimulating to the senses. Tapas and cocktails are a fine way to warm up to entrees for lunch and dinner. Bring the whole family or make it a date-night dinner, sit inside with air-conditioning or enjoy the chic street scenery on the cozy patio.</string>
    <string name="hoxton_pub">Hoxton Pub</string>
    <string name="antik">Antik</string>
    <string name="jazz_cafe_club">Jazz Café Club</string>
    <string name="stereo_sushi">Stereo Sushi</string>
    <string name="vertigo">Vértigo</string>
    <string name="hoxton_pub_description">The Hoxton Pub is a typical English style pub, bar and restaurant located in Barrio Escalante, San José. Typical of most English pubs, the focus is on traditional English cooking and beer drinking. The Hoxton food menu has all the British favorite pub fare. If your looking for a place to feel British in Costa Rica and enjoy some fish ’n’ chips with Guinness, the Hoxton Pub is highly recommended.</string>
    <string name="antik_description">Antik has three areas: The Basement has the best acoustics in the house and it\'s the main stage used to showcase international and local DJ\'s. The balcony is the ideal setting to admire some Central Valley views, a summer barbecue session or an evening of dancing by the city lights. Lastly, the Restaurant specializes in Italian cuisine and can host both small and large groups of customers.</string>
    <string name="jazz_cafe_club_description">Once the only place to check out consistently high-quality live music, especially jazz, in San José, The Jazz Café remains the best venue to see, hear, drink and eat under one roof. It is located in the San Pedro neighborhood, has a restaurant with good food and a full bar to go with the music. The shows vary from night to night, and past artists have included Mike Stern, Julien Lourau, Diego Urcola, Dennis Chambers, Frank Gambale, Steve Smith, and Scott Henderson, to name a few. You\'ll find tourists, expats, Costa Ricans, and an international crowd at the Jazz Café, so it\'s a nice place to socialize with musically like-minded folks in the city.</string>
    <string name="stereo_sushi_description">Stereo Sushi opened in 2015 on the 9th floor of an otherwise quiet apartment building, and quickly developed a reputation among university students as a \'sky club,\' illuminated in fluorescent blue light with DJs nightly. Sushi rolls and tempura are served until 11pm.</string>
    <string name="vertigo_description">Club Vértigo is one of the leading clubs in Central America. It has hosted some of the best parties with the worlds top Djs such as Deep Dish, Danny Tenaglia, Lee Burridge, Hernan Cattaneo, Steve Lawler, Marco Carola and Sasha just to name a few. It has been featured on famous electronic music magazines such as BPM and Club World. It has recently undergone a major makeover including a state-of-the-art sound system by Gary Stewart Audio (GSA).</string>
</resources>
